好，该结婚了
Okay,this is it.
你确定要这么做？
You sure you wanna do this?
你好，罗斯太太
Hello,Mrs. Ross.
你好，瑞秋先生
Well,hello,Mr. Rachel.
我的天哪
-Whoa! -Oh,my God!
菲比快点！快快快 好啦好啦
Come on,Phoebe,hurry!Okay! Okay!
我的天哪！大家都要结婚吗？
Oh,my God! Is everybody getting married?
教堂里不准奔跑
No running in the chapel.
你少跟我来这…
Hey,don't you give me any of your.. Hey!
你们来干什么？
Why are you here?
罗斯和瑞秋留言说要结婚
Ross and Rachel left a message. They're getting married.
你们不是来找他们的吗？
-Isn't that why you guys are here?
当然是 不然我们来干什么？
-Yes. Why else would we be here?
怎么样？我们来晚了吗？
What happened? Did we miss it?
我们也没赶上
We missed it.
都是因为教堂里不能奔跑
Maybe you wouldn't have if you could run in the chapel!
罗斯和瑞秋居然结婚了
I can't believe they got married.
对啊，我还不知道他们复合了
I know! I didn't even know they were dating.
与其说是复合 不如说是被伏特加附身
I don't think they're as much dating as they are...two bottles of vodka walking around in human form.
真是太疯狂了
This is insane.
有什么关系？又不是真结婚
What's the big deal? It's not like it's a real marriage.
什么？
What?
在拉斯维加斯结婚只有在拉斯维加斯有效
If you marry in Vegas,you're only married in Vegas.
你在说什么？ 在拉斯维加斯结婚到处都有效
If you marry here,you're married everywhere.
真的？ 是啊
Really?Yeah.
我的天呀…啊随便啦
Oh,my God!Oh,well.
本集播出：“离开拉斯维加斯”
The One After Vegas
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿阿奎特
寇妮考克斯阿奎特
丽莎库卓阿奎特
麦特勒布兰阿奎特
马修派瑞阿奎特
大卫修蒙阿奎特
我们为什么躺在一起？ 我不知道
Why are we in bed together?I don't know.
我们有… 我不知道
-Did we? -I don't know.
你有穿衣服吗？ 有
Do you have any clothes on?Yes.
真的 没有
-Really? -No.
但是我们没有…
But we didn't have..
做吧？
...sex,did we?
我不太记得昨晚的事
I don't remember much about last night.
一切都好模糊
It was such a blur.
我记得我有笑，我一直笑
I remember laughing. I laughed a lot.
而且我们没做爱
Then we didn't have sex.
罗斯，我们昨晚做了什么？
Well,so,what did we do last night?
我不知道，但我觉得很开心
I don't know,but I think it was a lot of fun.
幸好没有开心过头 应该没有 哦感谢上帝
Luckily,not too much fun,right?-I don't think so.-Oh,thank God.
我们真的醉得很惨 幸好没干什么蠢事
Oh,I mean,we were really drunk.I'm glad we didn't do anything stupid.
可不是吗
Tell me about it.
（新婚）
菲比早
Morning,Phoebe.
我的电影正式取消拍摄了
Well,my movie has been officially canceled.
真为你难过乔伊 你要不要吃我的早餐？
Joey,I'm so sorry.You want my breakfast?
不了，我沮丧得吃不下
Too depressed to eat.
过5分钟再说吧
I'll probably eat in,like,five minutes.
我只好跟你们回去了 飞机是几点？
I'll fly home with you. What time is your flight?
我的计程车呢？ 我用不着了
-What about my cab? -I don't need that anymore.
你跟我借车就要开回去
You borrowed my cab. You have to drive it back.
我不想自己开回去，太寂寞了
I don't wanna drive back by myself. I get lonely.
干脆你来陪我 我不晓得，要开很久
How about if you come with me?-It's a long trip.
一定很好玩 我们可以聊天玩游戏
-That would be great.We could talk and play games.
这是让友谊变新鲜的好机会
This could be our chance to,like,renew our friendship.
你要我跟你“友谊复兴”？
Are you asking me to have a "frienaissance"?
是吧？
Sure?
好吧，虽然没这个必要 我一直爱着你
All right. Although,I don't think we need one. I never stopped loving you.
有谁跟盖勒博士夫妇讲过话？
So has anybody talked to Dr. and Mrs. Geller yet?
他们有留言给我，应该快到了
They left me a message. They'll be here.
服务生呢？我饿死了
Where is the waitress? I'm starving.
这是自助餐
It's a buffet,man.
我可以捞本了
Here's where I win all my money back!
我有事找你 好，什么事？
I gotta talk to you.Sure.What's up?
莫妮卡和我昨晚差点结婚
Monica and I almost got married.
天哪！这可是大事
My God!That's huge!
等等，为什么没找我去？
Wait a minute. Why wasn't I invited?
谁要当你的伴O？ 不要说罗斯，不准说罗斯
And who was gonna be your best man? Don't say Ross. Do not say Ross.
我觉得我们还没准备好
I just don't think that Monica and I are ready yet.
我很爱她 但看到罗斯他们从教堂冒出来
I love her...but seeing Ross and Rachel come out of that chapel...
我突然惊觉我们进展得太快了
...was like a wake-up call that Monica and I are moving so fast,you know.
我要怎么讲才不会让她心碎？
How do I tell her without crushing her?
就说她不是结婚的料
Tell her she's not marriage material.
什么？
What?
女生都这么对我说
Girls say it to me all the time.
相信我，要是她和我一样 一定会如释重负
And if she's anything like me,she's just gonna be relieved.
我该怎么说这样太快了？
How do I tell him that it's too soon?
他一定会心碎 觉得我不爱他了
He's gonna think I don't love him anymore.
你是不爱他了 我爱
-Well,you don't. -Yes,I do.
很好，我只是在测试你
Good. I was just testing you.
我们才刚聊到培根火腿
We were just talking about bacon.
不对，我们是在聊网球 网球比较像真的
No,we were talking about tennis.Tennis is more believable.
谢谢
Thank you.
要咖啡吗
Coffee.
怎样？ 你们要谈谈昨晚的事吗？
What?Are we gonna talk about what you guys did last night?
昨晚什么事？昨晚又没怎样
What do you mean "last night"? Nothing happened last night.
罗斯把大家都找去看了
Ross invited us all to watch.
你有病啊？
What is the matter with you?
瑞秋 我们不可能错过朋友的婚礼
We weren't gonna miss our friends getting married.
谁结婚了？
Who got married?
你们啊
You did.
什么？拜托，我们哪有结婚 怎么可能，别闹了
What?-Hello. We didn't get married. -No,we didn't. That's ridi..
等等…我记得去过教堂
Wait,wait,wait. I remember being in a chapel.
我们醉成那样，不可能被批准
They would not let us get married when we were that drunk.
当然可能 在拉斯维加斯结婚的人通常都醉了
They let you get married.Most people who marry in Vegas are drunk.
我现在就醉了
Now,I'm drunk right now.
早餐不能喝鸡尾酒啊？ 我在度假
I can't have a mimosa with breakfast? I'm on vacation.
你们要怎么办？ 看来得找个离婚律师了
What are you gonna do?Well,I guess we find a divorce lawyer.
我想罗斯已经有一个了
Well,I think.. I think Ross already has one.
对，那家伙总算可以有足够的资金盖游泳池了
Yeah,that guy's finally gonna be able to put in that pool.
好
Okay.
这次会免费吧？ 你办了两次，所以会送一次
Now,this one's free,right? Because you paid for the first two.
你笑吧，丢脸的是你
Laugh it up,but the joke's on you...
我们不必离婚，只要办理注销（意同“切除”）
because we don't need to get divorced.We're just gonna get an annulment.
切除？罗斯，我想手术可解决不了问题
-An annulment?Ross,I don't think surgery is the answer here.
那是你的标记
Oh,that's your thing!
什么？ 你的标记
What?Your thing.
你是专门离婚的人 没错
You're the guy who gets divorced.
那才不是我的标记 我并不爱离婚
No,no,that's not "my thing."I do not love getting divorced.
你当然爱，这是你第三次离婚
Yes,you do. This is your third divorce.
你爱离婚爱到搞不好会娶它
You love divorce so much,you're probably gonna marry it...
然后婚姻破裂，你又得离婚 离婚名人
...and then it won't work out,so you're gonna have to divorce it.
我醉得好厉害
I'm so drunk.
要不要玩百高？ 好吧
-You wanna play some Pai Gow? -Maybe.
但我有点想谈谈昨晚的事 好主意，我也想谈
But I kind of think we should talk about last night.That's a good idea. I wanna talk about last night too
而且我不知道百高是什么。-没错
-and I don't know what Pai Gow is. -I see.
你觉得我们应该怎么办？ 不知道
-So what should we do? -I don't know.
但我知道我爱你 我也知道我爱你
I know I love you.I know I love you.
那我们还要回过头去结婚吗？ 我爱你
Where are we on the whole "going back to where they have the marriages" thing? I love you.
问得好
That's a good question.
昨晚我们让色子决定
Last night we let the dice decide.
也许应该再让命运决定一次 我爱你
We should leave it up to fate again. I love you!
没错，有征兆我们才结婚
We don't get married unless there's a sign.
要是你又掷出八来 就表示我们绝对应该结婚
So say...you roll another eight,then there's a sign，that we should marry.
好，八就结婚 2、3、4、5、6、7、9、10、11、12就不结
Eight we get married but 2,3,4,5,6,7,9,10,11,12,we don't get married.
听起来不错 好
Sounds great.
有人要掷了，请押注
Hey,we got a shooter.Money,please.
好了吗？ 好了
-Ready? -Ready.
来个八吧
Come on,eight.
没错，八
Yes,yes,eight.
八，简单八
Eight,easy eight.
居然真的是八 真是太不可能了
-I can't believe I rolled an eight. -That was so unlikely.
那就结婚吧…我猜
Let's get married.I guess.
等等，那不是难的八 我昨晚掷的是难的八
Last night I rolled a hard eight.
没错，这个八不对 不能结婚了，妈的
It was the wrong kind of eight. No wedding! Damn it!
我好想结婚喔
I wanted it so bad!
收拾行李去？ 好
Wanna go pack?
我们没做错吧？
We're doing the right thing.
当然没错，我们让命运决定
Of course we are.We left it up to fate.
如果我们应该结婚 一定会有明确的征兆
If we were supposed to get married,there would be a sign.
好，你还剩十九个问题 要好好把握
Okay,you have 19 questions left. Use them wisely.
快点，你不问就…不能赢了！
Come on,Joey. You can't win if you don't ask any questions!
怎样啦 你说会很好玩
-What? -You promised me a fun road trip.
结果我们开了6小时 你就睡了5个小时半
We've been on the road for 6 hours,and you've been asleep for 5 and a half.
下一个休息站就换手 你给我一路开回去
We are switching,and you are going to drive back.
这是对你的惩罚，贪睡鬼
That will be your punishment,you greedy sleeper!
好啦
All right.
现在你得唱歌给我听
And until then,you are going to sing to me...
因为收音机坏了，你又很自私 但歌声很好听
...because the radio's broken and you are selfish,but you have a nice voice.
是喔？我不… 快唱
-Really? I don't… -Sing!
我想彻夜摇滚
I wanna rock 'n' roll all night
真是个漫长的旅程
Man,this is a long drive.
我的眼睛有睁开吗？没有！
Are my eyes open?No!
早安
Morning.
嗨，伙计
-Hey. -Hey,hubby.
我想找你讨论注销婚姻的事
Actually,I wanted to talk to you about that whole annulment thing.
我不打算去办
Yeah,I'm not gonna do that.
好，那我们就维持婚姻关系
Okay.So we'll just stay married.
没错 我会请大家叫我盖勒太太
Yes,exactly.And I will make everyone call me Mrs. Geller.
真是太棒了 我还以为得加把劲说服你
Wow,this is so amazing.I really thought I'd have to talk you into this more.
我现在怕了 因为你好像不是在说笑
Now I'm scared because I don't actually think you're kidding.
我不是啊
I'm not kidding.
我不能有三次失败的婚姻 我不能，好吗？
Look...I can't have three failed marriages.I can't,okay?
我不要当那个人
I am not gonna be that guy.
我不要有这个“我的标记”
Okay? No,no. That is not gonna be "my thing."
所以我们要永远这样下去？ 我不知道
So,what,we just stay married forever?I don't know.
我还没想清楚 我知道这样有点夸张
I mean,I haven't worked it all out yet,but....Okay,I know it's a bit crazy..
说真的，你有什么影响？
How is this going to affect you,really?
偶尔填表格要打勾时 你就勾“夫人”那一格
I mean,you fill some form out once in a while...instead of checking the box "Miss," you check the box that says,"Mrs."
就在“小姐”旁边
It's right next to it.
好，抱歉，你说得对 我们确实可以维持现状
Okay. I'm sorry,you're right. You know what?We can stay married
我还以为那两格离得很远
because I thought that the boxes were far away from each other.
不是… 罗斯！
-No,they're right.. -Ross!
请你静下来 想一想你在叫我做什么
All right. Just...please take a moment here.and think about what you're asking of me. Okay?
我在请你帮我一个忙
I am asking you to do me a favor.
你是要我当你的老婆
You are asking me to be your wife.
而身为我的老婆 你应该帮我这个忙
And as my wife,I think you should grant me this favor.
我们发过誓了
We did make vows.
那个小孩踢得好用力 是你扯他的头发
That kid kicked me really hard.Well,you did pull his hair.
他拿我的零食 我不想再争了
-He took my snack. -I'm not getting into this again.
好啦
Okay
说真的，真的很痛
All right,you know what? Hurts really bad.
我就叫你不要走路，来
Well,I told you not to walk. Here.There. There. Okay.
这没有任何含意吧？
-This doesn't mean anything,does it?
没有 好
-No.-Okay
你怎么可以让人搭便车？
How could you pick up a hitchhiker?
他搞不好是强… 强奸犯或杀人犯什么的
He could be a rap.. He could be a rapist or a killer or something.
你以为我没有先问过他吗？
Don't you think I asked him that before he got in?
我不理你了，你睡你的觉
I'm not talking to you. You go back to sleep.
你，你是强奸犯吗？ 不是
-And,you,are you a rapist? -No.
你喜欢车上游戏吗？
Do you like car games?
喜欢，你会牌照游戏吗？
Yeah,you know the license plate game?
我最喜欢牌照游戏了
I love the license plate game!
我也要玩，我也要玩
I'll play. I'll play.
不行，你需要睡眠，晚安
No,you need your sleep. Night-night.
听着，我知道你想找我谈
Listen. I know you wanted to talk to me...
但我有个办法 或许能让你愿意维持现状
but I have an idea that may make you wanna stay married.
我们去注册，礼物都给你
We register...and you get to keep all the presents.
不行！罗斯，你听我说
No,Ross,come on. No,listen.
我一直在想要怎么表达
I've thought about how to tell you this.
结果想到一个池塘里的金鱼 在冬天冻死的比喻
I came up with an analogy about a little goldfish...in a pond that freezes over in the winter
后来又想到它是在谈 如何面对别人的挑剔
but I realized that was a story about what to do when people pick on you.
那个故事我打算写儿童书时用
So I'm gonna actually save that for my children's book.
瑞秋 是？
-Rachel？ -Yes？
你想说什么？ 抱歉
-What's up? -Oh,sorry.
总之我们不能维持婚姻关系
The bottom line,Ross...is we cannot stay married.
那可不一定 当然一定
-I don't know if that's true.. -Oh,but it is.
你知道吗？这就叫做意见不合
Okay. You know what this is?This is a difference of opinion.
在婚姻中遇到这种状况…
-When that happens in a marriage..
罗斯，这不是婚姻 这是全世界最惨的宿醉
Ross,come on!This is not a marriage! This is the world's worst hangover!
如果你不去注销，我也会去
Ross,listen,if you do not get this annulment,I will.
好，我去就是了 谢谢
All right. All right,I'll do it.Thank you.
对了 我们是否能有一个解除婚约聚会？
Hey，Hey，is there any such thing as an annulment shower?
等等，火车站在那里 我该下车了
There's the train station. This is where I get off.
我有你的住址和电话号码
I have your address and phone number.
我知道你的名字和你居无定所
I have your name and the fact that you're a drifter.
主动权在你手上
So ball's pretty much in your court.
好，再见，菲比
All right. See you,Phoebe.
拜托啦，菲比，我受不了了 求求你跟我说话
Come on,Phoebe,I can't take this anymore.Please talk to me.
让我补偿你
Let me make it up to you.
地面控制中心呼叫汤姆少校（歌曲《太空怪客》）
Ground control to Major Tom
倒数开始，发动引擎
Commencing countdown Engines on
吞几颗蛋白质丸 戴上头盔
Take your protein pills And put your helmet on
闭嘴，够了
-This is.. -Stop it! Stop it! No!
不公平，你明知我无法抗拒 那美妙的歌声
That's not fair. You know I can't resist that beautiful voice.
菲比，我真的很抱歉
Phoebe,look,I am so sorry.
我答应让你旅途愉快却没做到
I promised you a fun road trip with your friend...and I didn't deliver,okay?
现在我知道你认为保持清醒 对友情来说很重要
Now I know that you think being awake is an important part of friendship.
以后我会永远努力保持清醒
So I will strive to stay awake for as long as I know you.
你晚上还是可以睡觉什么的 谢谢
You can still sleep at night and stuff.Thank you.
那可以玩二十个问题了吗？ 我在堪萨斯就想到一题很棒的
So can we play 20 Questions now?I got a good one. I thought about it since Kansas.
好吧，是一种热食三明治吗？ 对
Okay.Is it a kind of hot sandwich? Yes.
是肉丸赛百味三明治吗？
Is it a meatball sub?
真不可思议！你是大师
That is incredible!You are the master!
真是够了 谁叫你必须要接的
-Enough already! -Well,you didn't have to catch them!
真好玩，你看起来就像要… 别说了，想都别想
-You look like you're.. -Don't say it! Don't even think it.
不说就不说 钱德，你跟她耗吧
All right.Chandler,enjoy your handful.
我们要不要干脆结婚算了？ 所有的征兆都叫我们结
Should we just get married?All the signs are telling us to do it.
我不想理征兆了
I'm sick of the signs.
这样太快了，我很满意现状 我也是
-I'm happy the way things are. -Me too.
我不想改变，你想吗？ 不想
-I don't want change,do you? -No.
好，那就不要改变 一切维持现状
Then nothing changes! Everything stays the same!
你快去整理行李 已经3天了，我快捉狂了
Go unpack. It's been three days,and it drives me insane!
别激动，又不是要结…
Jeez,relax,it's not like we're mar..
要是我在这里整理呢？
You know,I was thinking,what if I...unpack here?
那你的东西都会在这里
All your stuff would be here.
要是我的东西都在这里呢？
...what if all my stuff was here?
那你就得跑来跑去
Then you'd be going back and forth all the time.
没道理嘛 好
Doesn't make any sense.Okay.
要是我们同居呢？ 你懂我的意思吧？
What if we live together,and you get what I'm saying?
同居？又没有任何征兆
Live together?There've been no signs for that.
我问你就是个征兆
Me asking is kind of a sign.
好！ 好！
Yes! Yes! Yes!
好，你等等
Okay. Okay,wait. Wait,wait,wait.
这是你的钥匙
Here's your key. Here's your key.
你得进行启用仪式，出去再进来
Now go out and christen it!Go out and come back in!
这扇门5年没锁了，不过，好吧
Door hasn't been locked in five years,but okay.
准备好了吗？ 好了
-Ready? -Ready!
有点问题，钥匙断了我进不去 等等
The key broke in the lock,and I can't get in.Wait.
我也出不去
Oh,my God,I can't get out!
这不是征兆吧 不是，是钥匙很旧了
-This isn't a sign! -No,it's a very old key!
钥匙太旧了 旧得不得了
-It's an old key! -Oh,my God,it's old!
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
你有抱着门吗？
Are you hugging the door right now?
没有
No.
好，我也没有
Yeah,yeah,me neither.
手续办得还顺利吗？
So did everything go all right with the annulment?
没问题，都办好了 罗斯，谢谢你
Oh,yeah. No problems. It's all taken care of.Ross,thank you.
你们要不要去看电影 好啊
Do you wanna go see a movie?-Yeah,why not?
菲比？ 不了，眼前就有一出
-Phoebe?-No,thanks. I've already seen one.
我去穿毛衣 好
Okay,I'm gonna get my sweater.
想不想听一件奇怪的事？ 时刻准备着
You wanna hear something weird?Always.
我没去办注销
I didn't get the annulment.
什么？ 我们还是夫妻
What?We're still married.
不要告诉瑞秋，待会儿见
Don't tell Rachel. See you later.
献给真的结婚的寇特妮与大卫
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
钥匙断在钥匙孔里 我会修，等一下
Key is stuck in the lock.I can fix it. Hold on.
让开
Watch out,watch out.
还是打不开 我还没弄完
It still doesn't work.I'm not finished.
漂亮，你的技术真好
Nice job,Joe. You're quite the craftsman!